<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>vocabulary - Tag - Young&#39;s Blog</title>
        <link>https://www.helloyou.ng/tags/vocabulary/</link>
        <description>vocabulary - Tag - Young&#39;s Blog</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-un</language><managingEditor>young@tellet.com (Young)</managingEditor>
            <webMaster>young@tellet.com (Young)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 22:15:49 &#43;1200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.helloyou.ng/tags/vocabulary/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>IELTS Speaking Vocabulary for Clothes</title>
    <link>https://www.helloyou.ng/ielts-speaking-vocabulary-for-clothes/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 22:15:49 &#43;1200</pubDate>
    <author>Young</author>
    <guid>https://www.helloyou.ng/ielts-speaking-vocabulary-for-clothes/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[It is in vogue (ɪt ɪz ɪn voʊg): Currently popular or in fashion.
It is fashionable (ɪt ɪz ˈfæʃənəbəl): Stylish and currently popular.
It is one of a kind (ɪt ɪz wʌn ʌv ə kaɪnd): Unique; unlike anything else.
It is trendy (ɪt ɪz ˈtrɛndi): Currently popular or in style.
Casual/formal clothes (ˈkæʒuəl/ˈfɔːrməl kloʊðz): Outfits suitable for everyday wear or relaxed settings (casual) versus outfits suitable for formal events or occasions (formal).]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>IELTS Writing Vocabulary for Medicine</title>
    <link>https://www.helloyou.ng/ielts-writing-vocabulary-for-medicine/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 00:42:23 &#43;1200</pubDate>
    <author>ChatGPT</author>
    <guid>https://www.helloyou.ng/ielts-writing-vocabulary-for-medicine/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Alternative medicine (ɔːlˈtɜːrnətɪv ˈmɛdsɪn): Medical practices that are not part of standard care. Examples include acupuncture and herbal treatments.
Traditional medicine (trəˈdɪʃənl ˈmɛdsɪn): Practices that have been passed down through generations, often based on cultural beliefs and practices.
Espoused system (ɪˈspaʊzd ˈsɪstəm): A system or belief that one promotes or adopts.
Western medicine (ˈwɛstərn ˈmɛdsɪn): A system of medicine based on scientific research and the use of medications and surgeries; often contrasted with traditional or alternative medicines.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>IELTS Writing Vocabulary for Culture</title>
    <link>https://www.helloyou.ng/ielts-writing-vocabulary-for-culture/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 20:45:09 &#43;1200</pubDate>
    <author>ChatGPT</author>
    <guid>https://www.helloyou.ng/ielts-writing-vocabulary-for-culture/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Borderless world (ˈbɔːrdərləs wɜːrld): A concept where geographical boundaries become less relevant due to technological advancements, resulting in increased connectivity and interaction between countries and cultures.
Globalisation is growing (ˌgloʊbəlaɪˈzeɪʃən ɪz ˈgroʊɪŋ): The increasing interconnection and interdependence of the world’s economies, societies, and cultures.
Demolished barriers (dɪˈmɑːlɪʃt bærɪərz): The removal or reduction of obstacles or hindrances, often in the context of communication, trade, or cultural exchange.
Cultures transcend national boundaries (ˈkʌltʃərz trænˈsɛnd ˈnæʃənəl ˈbaʊndəriz): Cultural elements and influences are not confined to a single country but spread and are shared across borders.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
