<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>chart - Tag - Young&#39;s Blog</title>
        <link>https://www.helloyou.ng/tags/chart/</link>
        <description>chart - Tag - Young&#39;s Blog</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-un</language><managingEditor>young@tellet.com (Young)</managingEditor>
            <webMaster>young@tellet.com (Young)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 21:08:36 &#43;1200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.helloyou.ng/tags/chart/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>IELTS: Words and Phrases to Describe Trends</title>
    <link>https://www.helloyou.ng/ietls-words-and-phrases-to-describe-trends/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 21:08:36 &#43;1200</pubDate>
    <author>Young</author>
    <guid>https://www.helloyou.ng/ietls-words-and-phrases-to-describe-trends/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Upwards Trend Noun Adjective + noun Verb + adverb a rise a sharp increase increased sharply an increase a considerable increase increased considerably a peak a substantial increase increased substantially an exponential increase increased exponentially a dramatic increase increased dynamically a slight increase increased slightly a gradual increase increased dradually a marginal increase increased marginally a minimal increase increased minimally a steady increase increased steadily Downward Trend Noun Adjective + noun Verb + adverb Verb a decrease a sharp decrease decreased sharply plummeted a fall a considerable decrease decreased considerably plunged a drop a substantial decrease decreased substantially a decline a precipitous decline declined precipitously a dip a dramatic decrease decreased dramatically a plunge a marginal fall fell marginally a minimal drop dropped marginally a gradual fall fell gradually a slight decrease decreased slightly a steady decrease decreased steadily Phrases - Trend remained the same levelled off at remained constant kept the same at remained the same at stable trend kept stable at Phrases - Not Stable Trend unstable trend irregular trend fluctuating trend ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Average Temperature and Rainfall in Dubai</title>
    <link>https://www.helloyou.ng/average-temperature-and-rainfall-in-dubai/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 21:32:13 &#43;1200</pubDate>
    <author>ChatGPT</author>
    <guid>https://www.helloyou.ng/average-temperature-and-rainfall-in-dubai/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Average Temperature and Rainfall in Dubai Introduction:
The table and line graph present the monthly variations in average temperature and rainfall in Dubai throughout the year. The purpose of these surveys is to discern patterns and correlations between temperature and precipitation over the course of a year. The units of measurement are degrees Celsius for temperature and centimeters for rainfall. The data has been collated from the Dubai Meteorological Department.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
