<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>writing - Tag - Young&#39;s Blog</title>
        <link>https://www.helloyou.ng/tags/writing/</link>
        <description>writing - Tag - Young&#39;s Blog</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-un</language><managingEditor>young@tellet.com (Young)</managingEditor>
            <webMaster>young@tellet.com (Young)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 22:58:59 &#43;1200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.helloyou.ng/tags/writing/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Writing Vocabulary: Literacy</title>
    <link>https://www.helloyou.ng/writing-vocabulary-literacy/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 22:58:59 &#43;1200</pubDate>
    <author>Young</author>
    <guid>https://www.helloyou.ng/writing-vocabulary-literacy/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Literacy /ˈlɪtərəsi/: The ability to read and write.
&ldquo;Promoting literacy in underdeveloped regions is essential for economic growth.&rdquo;
Literate /ˈlɪtərət/: Being able to read and write.
&ldquo;Being literate in today&rsquo;s world opens up a myriad of opportunities.&rdquo;
Illiteracy /ɪˈlɪtərəsi/: The inability to read or write.
&ldquo;Despite advancements in education, illiteracy remains a significant problem in many parts of the world.&rdquo;
Screen media /skriːn ˈmiːdiə/: Content consumed through screens such as movies, TV shows, video games, and online content.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Writing Task1: Charts Illustrating the Relationship Between Different Travel Purposes and Preferred Destinations</title>
    <link>https://www.helloyou.ng/writing-task1-charts-illustrating-the-relationship-between-different-travel-purposes-and-preferred-destinations/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 23:41:30 &#43;1200</pubDate>
    <author>Young</author>
    <guid>https://www.helloyou.ng/writing-task1-charts-illustrating-the-relationship-between-different-travel-purposes-and-preferred-destinations/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[My Writing: The statistical charts display the figures in numbers and the correlation between different reasons and destinations over the years from 1994 to 1998. In this investigation, 100,000 people from the UK participated. Overall, the survey shows that UK residents preferred travelling to Western Europe during holidays, and there was a steady increase except in 1994.
To begin with, the most notable feature was seen in the category of &lsquo;Holiday&rsquo; in 1994, with 15,246, and it increased dramatically by 1998, with 20,700.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Writing Task 1: Bar Chart Showing Four Modes of Transport From 1950 to 1990</title>
    <link>https://www.helloyou.ng/writing-task1-bar-chart-showing-four-modes-of-transport-from-1950-to-1990/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 00:58:27 &#43;1200</pubDate>
    <author>Young</author>
    <guid>https://www.helloyou.ng/writing-task1-bar-chart-showing-four-modes-of-transport-from-1950-to-1990/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[My Writing (Band 6.5): The bar chart displays the proportions of four different types used to commute to work in a European city. This survey was conducted every two decades, from 1950 to 1990.
Overall, it represents that, at the beginning of the survey, more eco-friendly tools, such as walking and bicycles, were the primary modes of transportation, whereas commuting by car became the principle means at the end of the investigation.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Writing Vocabulary: Gender Issues</title>
    <link>https://www.helloyou.ng/writing-vocabulary-gender-issues/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 22:47:53 &#43;1200</pubDate>
    <author>Young</author>
    <guid>https://www.helloyou.ng/writing-vocabulary-gender-issues/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Attaining gender equality (əˈteɪnɪŋ ˈdʒɛndər ɪˈkwɒlɪti): The process of achieving equal opportunities and rights for all genders, particularly in social, political, and economic aspects.
Sexual discrimination (ˈsɛksjʊəl ˌdɪskrɪˈmɪneɪʃən): Unfair treatment or prejudice based on an individual&rsquo;s sex or gender.
A male-gender-biased society (ə meɪl-ˈdʒɛndər-ˈbaɪəst səˈsaɪəti): A society that favors men and is unfair to women or non-binary individuals in terms of rights, opportunities, and social roles.
Second-class citizens (ˈsɛkənd klɑːs ˈsɪtɪzən): Refers to individuals who are systematically discriminated against within a state or other political jurisdiction, despite their nominal status as citizens or legal residents.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Writing Task 1: Words and Phrases to Describe Trends</title>
    <link>https://www.helloyou.ng/writing-task1-words-and-phrases-to-describe-trends/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 21:08:36 &#43;1200</pubDate>
    <author>Young</author>
    <guid>https://www.helloyou.ng/writing-task1-words-and-phrases-to-describe-trends/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Upwards Trend Noun Adjective + noun Verb + adverb a rise a sharp increase increased sharply an increase a considerable increase increased considerably a peak a substantial increase increased substantially an exponential increase increased exponentially a dramatic increase increased dynamically a slight increase increased slightly a gradual increase increased dradually a marginal increase increased marginally a minimal increase increased minimally a steady increase increased steadily Downward Trend Noun Adjective + noun Verb + adverb Verb a decrease a sharp decrease decreased sharply plummeted a fall a considerable decrease decreased considerably plunged a drop a substantial decrease decreased substantially a decline a precipitous decline declined precipitously a dip a dramatic decrease decreased dramatically a plunge a marginal fall fell marginally a minimal drop dropped marginally a gradual fall fell gradually a slight decrease decreased slightly a steady decrease decreased steadily Phrases - Trend remained the same levelled off at remained constant kept the same at remained the same at stable trend kept stable at Phrases - Not Stable Trend unstable trend irregular trend fluctuating trend ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Writing Task 1: Describing Trends</title>
    <link>https://www.helloyou.ng/writing-task1-describing-trends/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 20:24:32 &#43;1200</pubDate>
    <author>Young</author>
    <guid>https://www.helloyou.ng/writing-task1-describing-trends/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[DESCRIBING TRENDS UP
rise (v): Production costs rose to their highest level of the year in July. rise (n): There was a rise in production costs to the highest level of the year. go up (v): Between 1900 and 2000, the population went up by over a million people. grow (grew, grown) (v): The number of first-time users grew rapidly in 2017. growth (n): There was solid growth in the number of first-time users in 2015.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Charts Showing Different Causes of Death in the USA for Two Different Years</title>
    <link>https://www.helloyou.ng/writing-task1-charts-showing-different-causes-of-death-in-the-usa-for-two-different-years/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 02:02:56 &#43;1200</pubDate>
    <author>Young</author>
    <guid>https://www.helloyou.ng/writing-task1-charts-showing-different-causes-of-death-in-the-usa-for-two-different-years/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Task 1: 150 words, 20 minutes The charts below show different causes of death in the USA for two different years. Write a report for a university lecturer describing the information shown below. Causes of Death in the USA My Writing The pie charts display the proportion of six primary culprits of death in the USA, and this survey was conducted in 1975 and 2002.
Overall, heart disease and &lsquo;other&rsquo; were the root causes of death throughout the survey, while lung disease showed the least.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Writing Vocabulary: Medicine</title>
    <link>https://www.helloyou.ng/writing-vocabulary-medicine/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 00:42:23 &#43;1200</pubDate>
    <author>ChatGPT</author>
    <guid>https://www.helloyou.ng/writing-vocabulary-medicine/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Alternative medicine (ɔːlˈtɜːrnətɪv ˈmɛdsɪn): Medical practices that are not part of standard care. Examples include acupuncture and herbal treatments.
Traditional medicine (trəˈdɪʃənl ˈmɛdsɪn): Practices that have been passed down through generations, often based on cultural beliefs and practices.
Espoused system (ɪˈspaʊzd ˈsɪstəm): A system or belief that one promotes or adopts.
Western medicine (ˈwɛstərn ˈmɛdsɪn): A system of medicine based on scientific research and the use of medications and surgeries; often contrasted with traditional or alternative medicines.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Writing Task 2: Should More People Be Encouraged to Wear Their Traditional Clothes Every Day</title>
    <link>https://www.helloyou.ng/writing-task2-should-more-people-be-encouraged-to-wear-their-traditional-clothes-every-day/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 20:44:18 &#43;1200</pubDate>
    <author>YouChat</author>
    <guid>https://www.helloyou.ng/writing-task2-should-more-people-be-encouraged-to-wear-their-traditional-clothes-every-day/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Wrting Task 2: 250 words, 40 minutes &ldquo;In many countries, people no longer wear their traditional costumes. They are forgetting their history and traditions. More people should be encouraged to wear their traditional clothes every day. Do you agree or disagree?&rdquo; 1. Introduction
Background: With modernisation, the use of traditional clothes is becoming more and more uncommon. Introduce Question: Some are of the opinion that wearing traditional clothes on a daily basis should be fostered, while others differ in opinion.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Writing Task 2: Will Globalisation Inevitably Lead to a Total Loss of Cultural Identity?</title>
    <link>https://www.helloyou.ng/writing-task2-will-globalisation-inevitably-lead-to-a-total-loss-of-cultural-identity/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 22:00:18 &#43;1200</pubDate>
    <author>ChatGPT</author>
    <guid>https://www.helloyou.ng/writing-task2-will-globalisation-inevitably-lead-to-a-total-loss-of-cultural-identity/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Writing Task 2: 250 words, 40 minutes As communication and transport continue to grow, societies are becoming more and more alike, leading to a phenomenon known as globalisation. Some people fear that globalisation will inevitably lead to a total loss of cultural identity. To what extent do you agree or disagree? Agreement Agreement: Globalisation and Loss of Cultural Identity Introduction In an era dominated by rapid advancements in communication and transportation, the world is becoming increasingly interconnected.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
